The world is still — soft light, cool air, the hush before the day begins.
Wan doesn’t cry. Doesn’t reach. Just watches — as if releasing something long held.
One breath. One letting go.
It climbs — small, bright, untethered — into the vast, quiet blue.
And just like that — some things rise not to return, but to remind us how light we can be.
It began with a breath — light, unburdened, and entirely its own.
Gravity loosened its grip — not all at once, but gently, like a sigh.
It passed over borders no map draws — between what was known and what was possible.
Time bent around it — hours folded into minutes, distance into feeling.
Even as the world darkened, it held its light — not defiantly, but tenderly.
It didn’t vanish — it remembered how to belong to something larger.
And there — not gone, but changed — it found its name among the ancient ones.